cjfallon.ie 2017-11-28

# Online Privacy Policy | CJ Fallon

This privacy statement is provided by C J Fallon (referred to as “us”, “our”, or “we” in these terms) for the information of visitors (referred to as “you” or “your” in these terms) to our website.

C J Fallon is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy statement explains how we use the information we collect about you and how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information. In these terms, “third parties” means persons, firms or companies which are not subsidiary or associated or joint venture companies of C J Fallon.

## 1\. Who We Are

This website is controlled by C J Fallon. Registered Office address:  
Ground Floor – Block B,  
Liffey Valley Office Campus,  
Dublin 22,  
Ireland.

## 2\. Information gathered by us

**2.1** The information that you may be asked to provide enables us to supply you with further information about our company, products and/or services. It also helps us to contact you if you have requested products, further information or logged an enquiry.

**2.2** We may on occasion, collect additional personal information through our website, products and services.

**2.3** We may also use aggregated information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage and our products and/or services and we may also provide such aggregated information to third parties. You cannot be personally identified by aggregated information.

## 3\. Distribution of Data

**3.1** Any information that is gathered from visitors engaging with our website, products and services is used by us and possibly third parties unless you write to us or send us an e-mail requesting us not to divulge your information to a third party.

**3.2** If our business or any part of the business is sold or integrated with another business your data and information may be disclosed to our advisors and any prospective purchasers and their advisors and may be passed on to the new owners of the business or relevant parts of the business who may use such data and information for the various purposes given in this online privacy policy.

## 4\. Consent

**4.1** By using our website, products and services, you consent to the use of your information as set out in this online privacy policy. We may change our online privacy policy at any time. If we change our online privacy policy we will post the changes on this website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. We will also contact you should we make any changes so that you may have the opportunity to object to the changes so far as they relate to your data and information.

**4.2** Owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, there is a possibility that your information may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area. By submitting your information to us you consent to the these transfers.

## 5\. Use of Information

If you wish to know what information we hold on you please contact us by [e-mail](mailto:info@cjfallon.ie "E-mail C J Fallon Limited") or letter addressed to the Data Protection Officer, at the address set out in paragraph 1.

## 6\. Limitation of Liability

If you request us to remove your personal information from our database or you wish us to amend or change the information we hold about you on our database, we will remove or amend any such information on your request. Such requests should be made by e-mail or letter addressed to the Data Protection Officer, at the address set out in paragraph 1.

## 7\. Contact us

If you have any questions about this online privacy policy, how we run the website or your dealings with our products or services, please send your query via [e-mail](mailto:info@cjfallon.ie "E-mail C J Fallon Limited").

* * *

Updated: June 26th, 2017
